孩子们 在2011年的秋天
Kids, in the fall of 2011
我的所有朋友都在谈恋爱
all of my friends were in relationships.
所以当巴尼的哥哥詹姆士来看我们的时候
So when Barney's brother James came to visit
就有一个小小的空间问题
it created a slight logistical problem
我们真得要一个更大的卡座
We're gonna need a bigger booth.
我要去洗手间了
I'm gonna go to the loo
我不是真的要去
I don't actually have to go
我只是想要个我自己的座儿
I just want a seat all to myself.
嗯 你们有人想问
So, would anyone care to ask me where
诺拉和我晚上去哪儿吗
Nora and I are going tonight?
别问他 那是个陷阱
Don't ask him. It's a trap
-你们上哪儿 -老天 问啥问啊
- Where you going? -Come on, man, for God's sake!
去温柔乡 凯文
Bootytown, Kevin!
我们终于要去温柔乡了（我们终于要看对方光屁股了）
We are finally going to Bootytown.
这就是为什么我们不问他
And that's why we don't ask him.
我觉得我要在美长腿高速路上欢蹦乱跳一下
I'm thinking I'm gonna hop on the Long Thighland Expressway,
在美胸港口停下吃点东西
stop off for a nibble in Breastport,
然后 如果运气好的话
and then, with any luck,
我要在午夜时分停留在她的港口
I'll be pulling into the Pork Authority by midnight.
等等 你们终于要去温柔乡了
Wait. You're finally going to Bootytown?
你看 我们就是不想猴急 好吗
Look, we just don't want to rush anything, okay?
所以我们要等到她决定的时候再决定
So we decided to wait until she decides
去滚床单
to let me have sex with her.
就是今晚啦
And that's gonna be tonight!
你怎么那么确定
How do you know for sure?
哈 她之前说过了
Ah, something she said earlier.
你猜 宝贝
Guess what, my sweet boy,
我今晚给你准备了特殊的款待哟
I've got a special treat for you tonight.
哦耶 你要去温柔乡了
Oh, yeah, you're going to Bootytown.
哈喽 亲们
Hello again, my darlings.
巴尼 我希望你为今晚准备好了
Barney, I hope you're ready for tonight.
因为你要用你那些
Because you're gonna have to use muscles
好几年都没用过的肌肉
you haven't used in years.
是吗
I am?
没错
Yes.
而且我希望你家里准备些阿司匹林
And I hope you have some aspirin at home
因为你的屁股明天要疼翻天
because your arse is gonna be killing you tomorrow.
真的
It is?
没错
Indeed.
因为今晚
Because tonight...
我要穿上这个
I'm strapping on this.
我们去滑冰
We're going skating!
她的港口现在关门了
The Pork Authority's closed.
现在来看
Looks like it's Hand Central Station
你得靠双手去中央车站了 小盆友
for you, little buddy.
这么说那是你的特殊款待
So that's your special treat?
滑冰
Ice skating?
当然了
Of course.
在那之后我们要去滚床单
And after that, we're gonna shag.
我们要去滑冰了 各位
We're going ice skating, everybody!
翻译 加菲猪 Henry 47.4 Mr.Gao 校对：园丁姐姐 Andie
问我对诺拉的看法
Ask me what I think of Nora.
你觉得诺拉怎么样
What do you think of Nora?
可爱的女孩子
Lovely girl.
问我对诺拉真实的想法
Ask me what I really think of her.
你觉得诺拉真的怎么样
What do you really think of her?
朋友们 她很棒 真的
Guys, she's great, seriously.
别说了
Just drop it.
再问我一次
Ask me one more time.
你到底认为诺拉怎么样
What do you really think?
好吧 如果你们实在想知道的话
Fine! If you really must know,
我不喜欢巴尼跟她在一起
I do not like Barney with that woman!
高兴了吧
Happy?
你怎么能不喜欢诺拉呢
What could you possibly not like about Nora?
她的头发 她跟老鼠一样的小小鼻子
Her hair? Her mousy little nose?
她所有的一切都那么完美
The way she does everything perfectly?
我的意思是 她有哪儿不招人喜欢的
I mean, what's not to like?
不是我不喜欢她 是因为
It's not that I don't like her.It's just...
她是我们的老妈
She's our mom.
她是你们的老妈 你什么意思
What do you mean,she's your mom?
她的一切都跟我们老妈有点像
Everything about her is vaguely our mom-like.
英国口音
The British accent...
哈喽 亲们
Hello again, my darlings.
我老妈超爱朱莉·安德鲁
Mom's obsessed with Julie Andrews,
所以在我们还小的时候
so when we were growing up...
哈喽 亲们
Hello again, my darlings.
-过来嘛你 -嘿
- Come here, you. -Hey.
她拥抱他的那种方式
And the way she hugs him.
左手搂在脖颈上
Left hand on the nape of the neck,
右手在背上轻拍三次
three gentle strokes on the back with the right?
过来嘛你
Come here, you.
这是洛埃塔·斯丁森的招牌动作
Trademark Loretta Stinson.
关键在这儿
But here's the clincher...
猜猜 我的宝贝
Guess what, my sweet boy.
猜猜 我的宝贝们
Guess what my sweet boy.
今晚有给你的特别款待哟
I've got a special treat for you tonight.
今晚有给你们的特别款待哟
冰淇林
Ice cream!
他们来了 安静
They're coming.Be cool.
忘了我的大衣
Forgot my raincoat.
我倒是没忘（暗指TT）
That makes one of us.
好了 咱们走吗
Well, shall we?
走啊
We shall.
噢 别把你那舌头磨坏了 巴尼
Ooh, don't wear out that tongue, Barney.
别等我了
Don't wait up.
我的意思是 当然 巴尼睡过了
I mean, sure, Barney has slept
很多人的老妈
with plenty of other people's mothers.
可现在他要睡我们自己的老妈
But now he's gonna sleep with ours?
从心理学的角度考虑 和像你们父母的人厮守终生
Psychologically speaking,it's perfectly normal
是非常正常的
to wind up with someone like your parents.
托我老妈的福 我可能会和一个
Thanks to my mom, I'll probably wind up with someone
更爱我弟弟的人厮守终生
who loves my brother more than me.
呃 从心理学的角度上讲
Well, psychologically speaking,
我现在要吐了
I'm gonna go throw up now.
恶...
Oh...
呃 这孩子搞得
Ugh! This baby is making it
我都没法系裤子扣了
so I can't button my pants anymore.
呵 我觉得我爸爸在55年中
Big whoop.In 55 years,
一次都没系上裤子扣
I don't think my dad buttoned his pants even once.
不知怎么 即便是甜言蜜语
And somehow, despite sweet talk like that,
我都不觉得性感了
I don't feel sexy anymore.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我意思是 我觉得即便你肚子在发福
I mean, you're-you're even sexier now
你却越发性感了
that you're rounding out.
我是说 你更性感了仅仅是因为
I mean, you're even more sexy simply
你‘包容’了很多
because there's so much more of you.
只要你那跟小象一样大的
I'm never gonna get in the mood while
小埃里克森还在我肚子里冲啊顶啊
your mammoth Eriksen seed is muffin-topping
我就不会“性致盎然”
the bodiddly out of me.
你是说在孩子出来之前
Are you saying,"No erky-erky
我们都不做
until this baby pops out"?
好了 够了
Okay, that's it.
让你觉得“性致盎然” 现在就是我的使命了
I-I am making it my mission to help you feel sexy again.
我不在乎你会变得多胖
I don't care how much more bloated you get.
下一轮酒我去买
I'll get the next round!
凯文 耶 凯文 谢谢你
Kevin! Yay, Kevin, thank you!
这么说 泰德
So, Ted, you're cool
你跟凯文相处不错 是吧
with Kevin, right?
我知道最近他一直过来玩
I know he's been over a lot lately.
喔 是啊是啊 凯文棒极了
Oh, yeah, yeah, Kevin's great.
我的意思是 像不久前有一件事儿 还是挺怪的
I mean, there was, like,one weird thing the other day...
他就穿着平角短裤站在那儿
He was just standing there in his boxers?
是啊
Yeah.
我跟他谈谈去
I'll talk to him.
泰德
Ted...
说实话
be honest.
你愿意上莉莉 对吧
You'd bang Lily, right?
这样 晚些时候
So, later that night,
巴尼和诺拉去滑冰了
Barney and Nora went skating.
嘿 孩子 你知道你妈妈
Hey, kid, you know how your mom won't
为什么不让你在晚饭前吃冰淇林吗
let you have ice cream till after dinner?
就是因为这样 漫长的等待让冰淇林更好吃了 对不
But then the waiting kind of makes it taste better?
哥都等那碗冰淇林
Well, I've been waiting two months
等了两个月了
for that bowl of ice cream.
今晚 我就要和它滚床单
And tonight,I'm gonna have sex with it.
看啊 巴尼 单腿滑
Look, Barney, one foot!
喔
Oh!
孩子们 对于大多数人
Now, kids, for most guys,
这就代表约会结束了
this would have meant the end of the date.
但你们的巴尼叔叔可不是一般的人类
But your Uncle Barney is not most guys.
哥可以hold住
I can turn this around.
哇 这真让我印象深刻
Well, I'm impressed that you know
你居然认识一个24小时工作的牙医
a 24-hour dentist.
哦 是啊
Oh, yeah.
他还可以给你纹个身
He can also give you tattoos,
或者帮你报税改西装什么的
do your taxes and alter a suit.
不过我可不信任他去给我改西装 因为
But I wouldn't trust him with a suit 'cause...
说道喝一杯 你想去么
Speaking of drinking,you want to...?
算了 巴尼
No, Barney.
今晚我真是一个悲剧
Tonight's been a disaster.
我觉得我们该就此道别了
I think we should just call it a night.
别 别这样么诺拉
No! Come on, Nora,
你的牙也没怎么样啊 让我瞧瞧
your tooth can't be that bad.Let me see.
哪个是假的来着
W-Which is the fake one again?
你看上美极了
You look beautiful.
嗯
Mmm.
好吧 我可以再去喝一杯
All right, maybe I could go for one more drink.
棒极了
Great.
真是有意思
It's funny.
有时候那些最浪漫的时刻
Sometimes the most romantic moments
就这样从天上掉下来
can just creep up on you...
哥可以hold住
I can turn this around.
嘿 嗯
Hey, um,
我们应该之前就说清楚的
should've mentioned this before,but, um, Ted and I prefer
如果在公共区域的话 泰德和我希望房间里的人
that our guests remain fully clothed in
应该穿的衣冠楚楚一点
the public areas of the apartment.
听到了一下抱怨哦 亲
Been some complaints.
是泰德说了什么么
Did Ted say something?
哦 就是有点小小的抱怨啦
Oh, th-there's been some complaints.
不是在背后说什么坏话
Not pointing any fingers or anything,
就是希望你能把裤子穿好而已
but let's just keep those pants on, okay? Good talk.
这样 如果是泰德这么说的话
Well, if Ted said that,
我也要抱怨下 泰德的蛋蛋(Nuts也有呆瓜的意思）
I've got something to complain about, too: Ted's nuts.
是哒 泰德是有点神经兮兮的 但我不会说他就是
Okay, yes, Ted is a little neurotic, but I wouldn't say...
不不不 我说的是泰德的蛋蛋
No, no, no, I mean Ted's nuts.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
那又怎么样 这是他的公寓
So what? It's his apartment.
你怎么站在他那边了
You're taking his side?
等下 这不会就是那种典型的
Wait, this isn't one of those classic
你还是对那个即使分手仍然还是你室友
"You still have feelings for your ex-boyfriend,
的前男友有感觉
"who's oddly also your roommate,
顺便说一下现在为止我都很冷静
"which for the record I'm totally cool with,
即使所有人都告诉我我
"even though everybody tells me I've walked
我已经陷入了这个复杂的关系圈 是么
into a bear trap" things, is it?
不 我就是 感觉不好
No, I just, I feel bad.
泰德最近不太顺利
Ted's going through some stuff right now.
你看到的那一幕就是他这几个月来
You eyeballing his deal is the most action
最喜欢做的事
he's gotten in months.
我会对他好一点的
I'll be nice to him.
所以 我极力去想
So, I was trying to think of how
怎么才能最好的表达你在我心中有多性感
to best express how sexy you are to me.
一首歌还是一首诗
A song? A poem?
然后猛然间有一股灵感涌过 桌游
And then it hit me:a board game!
你就是不能懂女人
You just get women.
不不不 你会爱上这个的
No, no, no, you'll like this.
我们问一些色色的问题再接受一点挑逗的挑战
We answer risqué questions and perform spicy dares
来慢慢的让你打开你的美腿
to slowly move up your shapely legs.
我把它叫做百合花的幽径（lily也有百合花之意）
I call it Chutes and Lilies.
我感觉应该叫独占莉莉
I would've guessed Monopo-Lily.
耶 这感觉更好
Yeah, that would've been better.
好的 我们开始吧
Okay, game play.
掷骰子来看看谁先开始
Roll the dice to see who goes first,
放弃一次要罚一轮 适合二到六个玩家
forfeit a turn on a pass--intended for two-to-six players.
就在马修解释百合花的幽径怎么玩的时候
As Marshall explained the many rules of Chutes and Lilies,
莉莉想起了早些时候凯文在酒吧说起的话
Lily thought back to what Kevin said in the bar.
和像你们父母的人厮守终生是非常正常的
It's perfectly normal to wind up with someone like your parents.
于是莉莉想起了唯一一个她知道的
And then she thought of the only other man she knew
如此热爱桌游的人
who loved board games that much.
我带了疾病这款游戏（lily的老爹自己发明的）
I brought Diseases!
马修版吹牛
Marshgammon.
小狗大战管理员
Dog Fight Promoter!
追逐莉莉
Lilial Pursuit.
这就是这款游戏的玩法儿
And that's how you play the game.
哦 等一下
Oh, wait.
对了 我忘了告诉你
I forgot to tell you what happens
如果我走到了胸部社区
if I land on "community chest."
捏一捏哦
Honk-honk.
我就想回家
I just want to go home,
然后洗洗睡了
take a long bath and go to bed.
不
No!
我是说 别这样啊
I mean, come on.
我住的地方近多了
My place is so much closer.
我可以让你去洗个澡
I'll-I'll draw you a bath,
给你倒点香槟 你会忘却所有的烦恼的
pour you some champagne,we can forget all about this.
好吧 听上去不错
All right,that sounds good.
这澡洗的真舒服
That bath was wonderful.
-谢谢你  -别客气
- Thank you. - Of course.
你觉得我们是不是该去阳台
What do you say we go out on the balcony,
呼吸点新鲜空气呢
get some fresh air?
哦 听上去棒极了
Ooh, that sounds lovely.
多美的风景啊
What a beautiful view.
必须的
I couldn't agree more.
永别了 残酷的世界
Good-bye, cruel world!
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
哥可以Hold住
I can turn this around.
嘘
Shh.
哦
Ooh!
哦 约会之夜
Ooh! Date night.
你们知道么 我就只要回自己房间看看这部碟子就好了
You know what? I'll just,just watch this in my room.
已经在那儿吃了晚饭了 干嘛不在那儿看一部电影呢
Already had dinner in there,why not a movie?
你该加入我们
You should join us.
是啊 来吧
Yeah, join us.
不不不不 三个人就显得太拥挤了
No! No, no, no, no, no.Three's a crowd.
再说 你们也不会想看这部电影的
Besides, you guys wouldn't want to watch this anyway.
试试看么
Try us.
好吧 你们看过虎胆龙威了么
Well, have you seen Die Hard?
嗯 是的
Um, yes.
那就好 在里面演大反派的那家伙
Okay, the guy who played Argyle
推荐了这部关于硬币收集的纪录片
produced this documentary about coin collecting.
现在 我知道我的这位娇小的性感的老婆
Now, I know my sexy little lady can't resist
不能抵挡泡泡浴的诱惑的
a bubble bath,especially one
尤其是撒了玫瑰花瓣的泡泡浴
with rose petals.
哦 是啊 亲
Oh, thanks, baby.
你感觉给你来个性感的搓背怎么样
How about a sensual backrub?
额啊
Mm.
-我去  -怎么了 莉莉派
- Oh. - What's the matter, Lilypad?
你喜欢我帮你搓背的
You love my backrubs.
这 是的 我爱死了
Ah. I-I do... very much.
很好 因为我
Good, because I got you a brand-
给你买了一个全新的
new...
浴用丝瓜络
loofah!
哦
Oh, yeah!
用力 哦也
Rubs... oh, yeah!
看看电视里放的硬币收藏啊
Trying to watch the coin documentary over here.
嘿 泰德 找到陪你去演唱会的人了么
Hey,Ted,ever figure out who you're taking to that concert?
没
No.
-你想去么  -当然
- You want to go? - Sure.
-真的
-太棒了
- Really?
- Awesome!
就这么定了
It's a date!
现在 作为一个职业的心理学者的凯文
Now, Kevin,as a trained psychologist,
知道应该用一种非常合适的方式来表达心中的不满
knew the appropriate wayto voice his displeasure.
我认为我们应该坐下来平心静气的探讨一下
I think we need to calmly discuss
关于我们之间关系的事情
the relationship dynamics at play here.
你们俩过去有一段就算了
I'm uncomfortable with how close you two are
当室友还搞的这么亲近 这让我十分不爽
as roommates, given your particular romantic history.
相反的 他采取了另外一个途径
Instead, he took a different approach.
我擦 绝对没门儿
Aw, hell no!
如果你和我女朋友出去约会
If you can go on a date with my girlfriend,
我就在你的公寓只穿裤衩
I don't have to wear pants in your apartment!
我都等不及这个孩子出世了
I can't wait till this baby comes out
那样我们就可以开始继续制造一个
so we can get started on another one.
又一个了
Then again,
-干嘛要等呢 -额 等下
-why wait? -Ew, wait...
放开我
Get off of me!
擦嘞
Damn it!
自从凯文说
Ever since Kevin said
和像你父母亲的人厮守终生是很正常的
it's normal to wind up with your parents,
我 我就总把你想象成我爸
I... I keep picturing yo as my dad.
莉莉 那理论太疯狂了
Lily, that theory is crazy-town.
你怎么知道呢
How do you know?
因为我妈妈是个一米九的巨人
Because my mother is six-foot-three,
所以她一般都在杂货店买她的衣服
she buys her clothes at the drugstore,
而且她喜欢自己做饭吃
and she prefers to trap her own dinner.
我爱你胜于一切
I love you more than anything,
而且你没有一点像她
and you're nothing like her.
噢
Aw.
这就是你是怎么让一个女孩性致全开
Now, that's how you turn a girl on.
-么 -么
- Mm...- Mm...
然后马修又开始想到
But then Marshall really started thinking
那个关于凯文提到的理论
about Kevin's theory.
午夜小吃来了
Midnight snack.
午夜小吃
嗯
Mmm.
噢 爽
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah...!
我准备要翻滚
I am gonna rock...
你的
your...
世界啦
world.
太棒了
Yay.
如果有什么事情可以安慰你的话
If it's any consolation,
这个 呃 刚跳下去那人偷过我的华尔街日报
the, uh... the guy stole myWall Street Journal once.
所以说 要是没他的话 这个世界会更好美好吧
So... guess the world's kind of a better place without...
噢 天啊 这个夜晚被毁了
Oh, God, this night's ruined.
噢 你过来吧
Oh, come here, you.
是啊 这个夜晚真的是很难熬
Yes, it's been a very tough night,
但是我还是觉得我们可以hold住的
but I still think we can turn this around.
真的吗
Really?
为什么不呢
Why not?
没必要因为这些事而沮丧
No sense in letting things get us down.
那首歌是怎么唱来着
How does that song go again?
玫瑰上的露珠和小猫的胡须
♪ Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens ♪
明亮的铜壶和温暖的羊毛手套
♪ Bright copper kettles and warm woolen mittens ♪
打着结的棕色包裹
♪ Brown paper packages tied up with strings ♪
这些都是我最爱的东西
♪ These are a few of my favorite things ♪
当狗咬
♪ When the dog bites ♪
当蜜蜂叮
♪ When the bee stings ♪
当我感到悲伤时
♪ When I'm feeling sad ♪
只要想起我最爱的东西
♪ I simply remember my favorite things ♪
然后我就不会觉得
♪ And then I don't feel ♪
那么糟了
♪ So bad. ♪
妈咪 不要啊
Mommy, no.
宝贝 我想谢谢你来提醒我
I want to thank you,baby, for reminding me of
我是多么活泼的一个女人啊
what a vivacious woman I am.
是的
Yeah.
其实 不需要
No, uh, no need really.
哇 那要是我是一个非常淘气的女孩
Whoa, but I've been such a naughty girl.
或许我需要被打打屁股呢
Maybe I need a spanking.
那我们就
Great. We'll...
我们就跳过桌上游戏吧
we'll just skip the board games
然后躺下来让我好好疼爱你一下
and get right down to me making love to you.
噢
Oh...
那敢情好  因为
Okay, good, 'cause
我要像骑野马一样骑你
I'm gonna ride you like an unbroken stallion.
好吧
Okay.
驾 牛仔女郎
Giddyup, cowgirl.
不行 我不能做啊
No, I can't go through with this!
谢天谢地 我也不行
Thank God, me neither!
你实在是太像我的爸爸了
You're too much like my dad.
你也太像我的爸爸了
你爸爸
Your dad?!
好吧 脱掉裤子是个坏主意
Okay, dropping trou --bad idea.
那我们继续吧
We're moving on from that.
这个人太阴险了
This guy is a snake.
什么 不要
What?! No.
泰德 他是一个很好的人
Ted? He's a nice guy.
他真的是个很好 很好的人
A really, really nice guy.
你应该更加像他才对
You should be more like him.
妈 不出我所料啊
Mom, right on schedule.
什么 没什么
- What? - Nothing.
我只是说 你觉得他很脆弱
I'm just saying, you think he's so fragile,
而且 喔哦 等一下 你觉得我脆弱
and yet...Whoa, whoa, whoa, fragile?
你认为我很脆弱
You think I'm fragile?
是的 脆弱的就像只狐狸
Yeah, fragile like a fox.
第一 他试图用
First, he tries
他的蛋蛋秀吓到我
scaring me off with his little peep show.
然后他又毁了我们的电影
Then he crashes our movie.
现在 他有又几张非常浪漫的音乐会的门票
Now, he's got tickets to some super romantic concert.
明明是怪才维奇的
It's Weird Al Yankovic.
好吧 那到底谁是他第一个邀请同去的人
Okay. But still, who's the first person he asked to go with him?
我的女朋友
My girlfriend.
噢 老兄 好吧
Oh, man. Okay.
难道你认为我是泰德第一个邀请的人
You think I'm the first person Ted asked?
泰德 我是第一个问你的人么
Ted, am I the first person you asked?
马修
Marshall...!
你 我
You, me, Weird Al.
不用了 泰德
No thanks, Ted.
巴尼
Barney...!
我有两张去
I got two tickets to Weird Al Yan...
巴尼
Barney?
莉莉
Lily...!
拜托 你肯定会是那里最性感的女生
Come on! You'll be the hottest girl there!
呵呵 你会是那里唯一的女性
Okay, you'll be the only girl there.
斯图尔特（莉莉的初恋男友）
Stuart...!
克罗蒂亚（泰德的前女友之一）
Claudia...!
布拉德（马修的同学）
Brad...!
娜塔莉（泰德的前女友之一，生日被甩妞）
Nat-alie...!
特鲁迪（泰德的前女友之一）
Trudy...!
兰吉特（出租车司机）
Ranjit...!
酒保卡尔
Carl the bartender...!
酒吧里的兄弟们
Dude from my bodega...!
发干洗店优惠券的朋友
Steam cleaning coupon guy...!
妈妈
Mom...!
好不好 我飞过去接你
Please? I'll fly you out.
我不想去
I don't think so.
真抱歉  小甜豆
I'm sorry, sweet pea.
克林特（泰德的继父） 在吗
Is Clint there?
不在
No.
哇 你真的很脆弱
Wow. You really are pretty fragile.
瞧 我试着向你们解释
Look, I'm trying to explain to you guys that I'm...
你们希望我有什么感觉
Well, how do you expect me to feel?!
我就是想
I mean, all I want
找个人跟我去听怪才维奇的演唱会
is for someone to go to a Weird Al concert with me,
我不得不跟我室友一起去
and I'm stuck going with my roommate.
是 我可能会改天跟你一起去 哥们
Yeah, I might have to rain-check you there, buddy.
我不是怪才维奇的粉丝
I'm not a Weird Al fan.
他只是加拿大怪才雅克的山寨版
He's just a rip-off of Peculiar Jacques.
意思是我要自己去听音乐会了
Guess I'm going to this concert alone.
我要成为一个古怪的人了
I'll be that weird guy.
我是说 另一个古怪的家伙
I mean, that other weird guy.
你知道不 有个人你还没有问呢
You know, there is one guy you didn't ask yet.
这个人凑巧就是怪才维奇全世界
Someone who happens to be the biggest Weird Al fan
最忠实的粉丝
in the whole world.
凯文
Kevin...?
泰德
Ted...!
哦 你要是看到我们的票 你会跳起来
Oh! Oh, you are gonna flip when you see our tickets.
它们的形状就像个手风琴
They're in the shape of an accordion.
什么
What?!
这  你喜欢怪才维奇
So, uh, you like Weird Al?
一点也不
Not in the slightest.
不 伙计 我就是怪才维奇最忠实的粉丝
No, dude, I'm the biggest Weird Al fan.
我知道 我同意
I know, I'm agreeing with you.
你知道我给他出的那个“像个外科医生”的点子吗 （恶搞麦当娜的名曲like a virgin 像个处女 ）
Do you know that I gave him the idea for "Like a Surgeon." Yeah.
是 我给他写了一封信 几个月之后
Yeah. I wrote him a fan letter, and then a few months later...
嘭 排行榜第一位
Bam! Top of the charts!
你们可以吃了 （恶搞迈克杰克逊的beat it)
You guys can eat it.
吃 就行啦
Just... eat it.
- Hey.  - Hey.
-嘿  -嘿
跟诺拉玩的怎样
How'd it go with Nora?
额 出了点意外
Well, among other things,
我觉得诺拉跟我妈妈很像
I realized Nora's a lot like my mom.
我该赌一下他们没成功
I'll bet that ruined things, huh?
来吧 巴尼斯丁森总是能hold住全场
Come on. Barney Stinson always turns it around.
-怎么弄  -简单
- How?  - Simple.
哥可以hold住
I turned...it... around.
哦 嗯哼 嗯哼
Oh... Uh-huh? Uh-huh?
所以这关于妈妈的事情没把你们的事搞砸吧
So the mom thing wasn't a total deal breaker, huh?
当然木有
No!
伙计们 我妈妈是我见过的最好的人
Guys, my mom is the best person I know.
如果诺拉哪怕有一点像她 我就很幸运了
If Nora's even the tiniest bit like her, I'm a lucky guy.
嘿 你知道吗
Hey, you know what?
我真的很幸运
I'm a real lucky guy.
因为我娶了我爸爸
'Cause I married my dad.
噢
Aw.
所以 额 你想更幸运一些吗
So, uh, you want to go get luckier?
再见 伙计们
Bye, guys.
再见
See ya.
额 我们干点什么呢
So, what should we do now?
我们什么也不要做
"We" should do nothing.
你们出去看你们的电影
You guys get out of here, go watch your movie.
我很好 真的
I'm fine. Really.
-你确定  -确定
- You sure?  - Yeah.
谢谢了 哥们
Thanks, buddy.
嘿 凯文
Uh, hey... hey, Kevin.
我现在觉得我像是一个克隆人
I think I'm a clone now.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
你刚刚是在模仿怪才维奇吗
Were you just quoting Weird Al?
当然是
I was indeed.
我是他的超级粉丝
I'm a huge Weird Al fan.
那我得给你买点喝的了
Well, then I need to buy you a drink.
我想要一杯香槟 小甜豆
I'll have a glass of champagne, sweet pea.
一杯香
One glass of champa--
小甜豆
Sweet pea?
当然 见到一个同是怪才维奇粉丝的人
Sure. Meeting a fellow Weird Al fan?
这是用来庆祝的
That's cause for celebration.
一瓶香槟 马上来
Bottle of bubbly, coming right up!
亲爱的维奇先生
"Dear Mr. Yankovic,
我的名字是泰德 莫斯比
"my name is Ted Mosby...
八岁了
"eight years old...
吃它 这首歌改变了我的生活
'Eat It' changed my life..."
什么 什么 什么的
Blah, blah, blah.
噢 开始了
Uhp. Here we go.
我有些主意可以给你写新歌用
"I have some ideas for new songs you could do."
他们怎么就不能让我一个人安静一下呢
Why can't they just leave me alone?!
在你跳单高跷前叫醒我 （恶搞Green Day的wake me up when september end )
"Wake Me Up Before You Pogo."
我得把一下午都耗在这破信上吗
Spend a whole afternoon on that one?
像个外科医生
"Like a Surgeon."
我终于从医学院毕业了（恶搞麦当娜的Like a virgin)
♪ I finally made it through med school ♪
无论怎样 我终于毕业了
♪ Somehow I made it through,ooh... ♪
文尼
Vinny!
开始录音
Start recording!